Thank you for watching!
Next Episode Trailer
Next Trailer
Good job... Mission accomplished immediately!
Oh, that's good.
Hey, you're dead.
You were dead.
Acarjozuki, you have to touch it again. It means he's not dead.
We'll use that. Bye.
Wow.
How does that ring a bell?
Well, that was fun.
Oh, that's a nice flow.
Okay, good. Good.
From a girl.
From the girls. From the girls.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm taking it, though.
I'm not taking it.
Keep it.
Keep it!
Kubo's going to make more moves.
It's just this... the last thing I ate at the last lunch box.
Con.
The limit is the box.
The topic of bento naturally led us to the catering space.
My favorite bento...
Oh, it's okay. I'm sure he'll enjoy it.
In an instant, the flippers were set on the front teeth.
And Umezawa is standing by here at the same time.
I'm going to take a break from the weight of my clothes.
It might go buzzy.
One more buzz.
While Kubo pulls back, Umezawa quickly gets ready.While Kubo is pulling away, Umezawa quickly begins preparations.
Four in the staff.
Four?
Wow!
That's great.
They're all going to fall for it, aren't they?
Mukai was completely unaware of Umezawa's final.
Wow!
That's the look on his face when the balloon bursts at close range!
And here comes Kubo with a tantrum!
Isn't this beautiful?
Isn't it somewhere?
Did you find it?
Wow!
You'd be surprised.
Hot, hot, hot.
So far, they're working together beautifully.
Now all we need is to get it to the finishing tub and we'll have mission complete.
I think I'll just pop it to Umezawa, get in, and go to bed.
Mukai is in super tricky mode, wanting to surprise the staff in a state of dependence.
Mukai, in his super tricky mode, wants to surprise the staff without any guidance, and heads for the door by himself.
Excuse me, Mr. Manager.
Asami!
You're lying.
That's not good.
That's funny.
He's serving it.
I love it.
Oh, my God.
He's got me.
What if this is...
Go, go, go.
So, the guy across the street is on his own.
The square guy's in the graveyard.Shikakunin ga Hazekake
Simplified
I can no longer go to anything across the street.
From here, it's an extended game
During the fake interview location
Ito's cardboard pop-up and
the second time to set up a tub drop.
The most expensive thing I've bought recently
Mouse pace.
It's pretty intense.
I was told by the shopkeeper that my teeth are chipped
I was told
It's 5,500 yen.
And to make sure I don't make 10,000 yen
Yoshida, while attracting the gaze of the person across from him
Yoshida forced himself to prolong his answer.
Wait a minute
No way!
You startled me.
How many times have I been surprised?
I can be surprised as many times as I want.
So, when the fake interview location is over...
Thank you very much.
I don't even have any shoes.
Thank you for your hard work
I'm celebrating by taking another shot at the comedy I just got... at a completely unmarked spot.
How was it?
It's a lot of fun!
It's raining really hard today.
I was stroking myself pretty hard, but I'm so glad I was able to participate in this fun project.
It was great last time!
The other side of the room and all the other participants were full of weirdos!
Next time, we'll see how many surprises we can throw at him.
No matter how many times I do it, I always get caught.
I'm the one who made it happen!I'm scared and I'm scared and I'm scared
Scary, scary, scary.
That's a killer!
The way those balloons go round and round, it's really scary.
I'm gonna stab him in the neck.
Next, the 5th term students!
First, Inoue tries 3 missions against Nakanishi.
Let's see what the 5th term students can do!
He led the smart Inoue berth naturally to his front.
Then, while he was surprised, he offered the "Biribiri Pen" to Inoue with a perfect flow.
What a perfect flow!
Ouch!
That's absolutely crazy!
Absolutely weird.
It's totally weird.
I'm scared.
What's wrong with me?
That really hurt.
It's like when you're trying to hide a Hikman.
That's not even close.
All that's left is the eye-drop mission.
I have to go get a drink without being seen by the target.
They're early.
They're already on alert.
What?
That's right.
This is alarming.
What?
It's too soon.
No exposure?
No dew?
Vancha is rescued due to a fatal mistake where the dewdrops are found on the target.
But by standing up, Nakanishi automatically...
Hey, seriously.
The boo-boos exploded again.Once again the boo-boos exploded.
Time ran out here.
As for the face dew...
Did you find anything difficult from Nakanishi's point of view?
I thought he was too timid in spite of the cold weather.
It's true... Asano Nagi is so low strung...
I wondered why she talked so much.
I wondered what was wrong with her.
Don't say that.
The first half was perfect.
The mission was not completed.
Next, Ogawa challenged Ichinose.
Against Ichinose, who has a hard time with Ogawa...
What kind of strategy will they use to accomplish the mission?
The target who doesn't sit down easily in the middle of the survey mission.
What about Ogawa here?
Is he the one who has it all around here?
Using magician's technique to distract Ichinose's natural enemy who won't sit down.
Boo-boo! Mission accomplished!
What?
Just like that.
Don't do that.
Why not?
You can't do that.
You're cute.
Do it again. Do it again.
No.
Why not?
Because Riko is an idol and she doesn't fart.
Aya laughs.
Aya laughs
There's a fart.
Just let it out.
Aya laughs
No, but he's right in front of you...No, but it doesn't mean he's going to die before your eyes.
It's not like he's gonna die.
Yes, it's really like this
Ichirinsei being manipulated so much as he wants.
And Ogawa made a super fine play by taking away two pens in the process.
Ogawa's scary.
Yay!
Great reaction!
That's great!
What? Is this a surprise?
You're getting all weird and evil.
Ichinose, a slave to the creek, is ready for anything.
So, I'm going to force him into a more aggressive position, and then...
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
If you eat your bento, there's always SCOLA!
Sneaking around the target's quadrangle to get some nori.
Natural.
Hanami Shiro
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Ooh!
Strongest ice cream
Mushroom cake
I've got some at home.
I got a freezer full of these.
Blah, blah, blah.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you today?
I told you something bad was going on, and you fell for it.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
The mission is not complete until...
Ichinose's madness has reached its peak.Ichinose's madness has reached its peak.
I'm forced to end it here.
Oh man, if you let him do it at all, who is he?
I thought it was funny.
Normally he doesn't talk to me.
Today, it's more like a truncheon.
You're good.
I'm good.
Not for you?
Ichinose's aggressive tactics worked.
Ogawa accomplished his mission.
Next, Ichinose!
The corner was a three-man challenge by Ikeda.
They aim to complete 3 missions to the target Tomisato.
First, he had to sit on a chair with his back to the cardboard
to sit on a chair with his back against the cardboard.
Oh, no!
Mr. Tomisato went to the other side to get a pen!
If I don't do this, the cardboard sheet will not move at all!
Oh, no!
Can you make it?
Ikeda interrupts unnaturally and steals a seat!
The target is forcibly lured to the opposite side.
Then, the cardboard box immediately starts moving!
Don't get caught.
It's because of the line before...
What was it?
I don't know...
What is it?
It's a disaster.
That's a good trick, isn't it?
What is it?
Yeah, something.
It's like there's a big piece of cardboard hiding in there.
Next, we're going for the kamakiri pose.
The mission is to make him pose with his whole body, not just his hands.The mission is to make you pose with your whole body, not just your hands.
This is the most expensive one.
I don't have a good image anymore.
My senpai buys me a drink.
I'm going to buy you a meal.
Graduated from Kuromi.
Oh?
Going from Kuromi was...
It was great.
We did that plate thing, right?
That's right.
What?
The fifth-year student's first anniversary.
That's amazing.
Kuromi's a great big sister.
Amazing.
She's amazing.
Kuromi taught my dad.
Oh my God, it's the first anniversary.
Oh my God.
You did it!
You did it, Kuromi.
Let's get serious.
Who'll be the first?
If you do it in private...
"Kamakiri"?
From the sudden "kamakiri" championship...
Tomisato...
Oh, something different
Kamakiri
Ah!
Which is it?
I didn't expect it to be the original kamakiri...
Mission failed.
Now if we could just get the tub...
I'd like to clear something.Something or other I'd like to clear up.
Oh, something.
He said, "Come here once, everybody.
With a false call.
To lead them out.
I'm sorry.
I can do this one time.
Say that.
You're watching me, aren't you?
Oh, no, that's...
Oh, no.
Oh, that's good
Wow!
Ew.
You were a trickster.
But do you really do this kind of thing all the time, Miku?
Not at all.
I didn't know.
You do that kind of thing?
It took three of us to boldly talk about the mission.
We get a new episode of Kuromina.
The next mission was to get the Boo Boo cushion from the sofa.
The next mission was to get the Boo Boo cushion from the sofa and start with water.
The more difficult version. And, as before, we'll take him out of the room first, and aim for a direct hit to the tub.
I tried to drink some kind of drink, but I'm going to try to drink it.
Oh, there's no booboo in this!
First, prepare a drink naturally
I reassured him with a cup of regular tea.
Wow! 17 minutes of it!
He said he made it by hand.
Isn't this amazing?
To get a refill right away.
Suddenly, he takes an unnatural gulp.
Inoue Oppuda's coordinated play.
Is this gone?Are these gone?
Maybe not.
Thank you.
You are very kind.
Thank you, Inoue-san.
Inoue here.
Iiyo kiyo only stand by for another menus.
It takes a lot of courage to put 10,000 yen in a watermelon
Boo hoo!
me
Taking advantage of the panic, Ninja Inoue quickly took the next action.
Mouth Balloons Group
Wow, that's great!
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Oh, it floats!
He demonstrated the technique of handing a tissue to the group to distract their eyes and sneak a cushion in a spectacular manner
Somebody notice that you...
He's taking his legs apart.
Oh, my God, they're all the same.
Oh, my God.
Oh!
Compendium.
The perfectly prepared boo-boo cushion is cleared of rotten hair!
Boo-boo cushion is no way for Motoi to live.
This isn't how it was supposed to be at first
I'm getting the feeling that I'm going to have to get him out of here and give him the tarai.
I'm getting some kind of call that they want me to come over soon.
Can you see it?
A standard lie call to call a good lie.
It's early.
5th student, 2nd place in physical fitness test, iyoki.
Beat him with a strong stomach twice, and mission failed.
Failed to take advantage of Kunouchi Inoue Nagi's covert action, 5th term student mission completed.
The relationship between the 5th term students is a work in progress.You know, the relationship between the fifth graders is a ready-made one.
You were just a slave.
I was shocked.
Was it weird?
Inoue's good at it, though.
I'm scared of you too.
Nakanishi was good at it too.
Be careful.
That was good.
I've been doing the Grand Prix. Why is there nothing weird going on?
I'm scared.
Do you guys like floating?
Why is something strange happening today?
I'm scared.
Scary, scary, scary!
Come on, now. Have you noticed anything?
What?
Inoue?
Inoue... a mole grew slowly and gradually during the recording.
Seriously? I didn't notice.
Inoue...
How are you doing?
It's all melted away.
You didn't even know I was standing next to you.
The sides are a little more cooperative.
You knew.
You didn't see Mr. Kimura?
I'm sorry, I didn't notice you at all.
You didn't know about the third term students?
But I thought maybe they were crying because Ken was teaching them.
There was a time when I did.
I had to talk to Inoue and the others at the end of the fifth term.
I had to talk to Inoue and others at the end of the fifth period.
Oh, really? I didn't see that part either.
So if someone watches TV and doesn't notice she's been pulled out...
Oh, she has a dirty face.Does she have a dirty face?
Yeah, she's really getting her face pulled out every once in a while.
She's been pulled out... by the person doing it.
There's more.
Not just one.
Wait, you're aware of it.
What?
You're talking too fast, Saku-chan.
You're lying!
No way!
You've been eating...
What did you eat during the show?
Cupstar.
This is what you were eating on the set.
I ate all of it.
I've already eaten everything.
That's cute, but scary!
We also had rice crackers and manjuu (Japanese sweet buns).
I didn't know...
I didn't know that.
No, I didn't know that at all.
I didn't know...
I didn't know you only noticed the sugar.
I turned around.
You know how Cupstar smells?
I don't know.
Yes, they do.
Cupstar smells good.
No, I don't know what a sizzle is.
I have no idea.
How do you do that?
Four seasons, that's all I know.
What?
I don't know.eh?
Oh, my God.
It's Rei, right?
What?
That's scary.
It's Ray, isn't it?
I don't know.
You dug it, didn't you?
Semya, did you do something?
I ate a rice ball.
I'm serious.
I ate a whole rice ball.
When did you eat it?
During the 5th term students' VTR.
Saki told me she couldn't finish it.
I couldn't finish it.
Wow!
I ate it because I couldn't finish it.
I didn't notice.
I couldn't see what was right in front of me.
You drop onigiri.
You can eat onigiri and cupsters?
If you try hard enough.
That's it for the fourth season.
Who do you think that is?
Who do you think it is?
It's a oyster.
Yes, sir.
Kaki.
I drank a can of Coke.
I was drinking a can of Coke.
Time out.
You're kidding.Oh, my God.
I'll start by opening it.
Oh, my God.
What's the sound?
What?
Sound?
That's why this is the first half.
When I was doing my VCR for the first half.
I open it up here and do it like this.
Seriously.
That's horrible.
I was drinking a Coke.
Just a Coke.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One Coke.
And there's three of us coming in and drinking.
That's right.
Over there.
Not bad.
That's great.
You don't even notice it when they do it on the set.
I don't have a third term.
That's weird.
Nothing.
Third trimester...
Third trimester?
I'm sure there will be.
I'm sure it's there.
If you've noticed something...
Then I'll give you a hint.
I'll give you a hint.
I've been working on it since before it started.
What?
Before it started.Before It Begins
Before it started
I'm sure you've noticed four or five.
What?
What, what, what, what?
Let's reenact it from the moment we walked in.
What?
Wait a minute.
We're coming in, aren't we?
Today.
Please.
It's already started at this point.
What? What?
Oh, okay.
Mr. Umezawa is on there.
What?
Wow!
Um, the plums are huge.
I don't get it.
It's too big. I don't know.
And they're going in stages, right?
Yes, we started with 5 centimeters.
Now we're down to 10 centimeters.
Oh...
So I'm 180.
But the original was 5, so now it's about 185.
What?
Seriously.
That's amazing.
That could be amazing.
See?
But you don't even notice it.But you don't notice.
No, I don't know. I'm too big to notice.
But...
But it's big.
Oh, but it's big.
But...
This is it.
Oh, but...
But aren't ume plums even bigger?
(laughs)
But...
Where did you change it?
In between breaks, I pretended to fix the microphone.
I changed my shoes.
Yes, I did.
I felt really uncomfortable during the break.
Why are we taking this break?
That's right.
I said... there's a break!
That's all.
Is there more?
There's more.
No, there isn't.
I don't have any.
You.
I wanted you to be awesome.
This is fun.
This is a great plan!
I just can't stop thinking about how awesome it is.
Now I'm thinking how scary this team is!
Now accepting applications for the third round of mobile selection for the Tokyo leg of the national tour!
I'm Haruka Kaki.
I'm Sakura Endo.
Please subscribe to our channel!Please subscribe to our channel!
điều입니다~!
Yes, bye!